-Here?
-Yeah.
-Are you fucking serious?
-Yeah, yeah. What did I tell you?
Incredible, right?
This is the oldest bar in New York.
No, that's McSorley's.
No, no. Landlord said
this is seven years older.
Pirates used to drink here.
There was, like, a brothel upstairs.
-That was how you found it, huh?
-Oh yeah.
-It stinks.
-Of course it does.
I mean, it actually smells, man.
Come on. I gotta get back to work.
No, Jake, come on.
Open up your fuckin' eyes.
You've got no vision. This is the place.
To do what? Murder a prostitute?
We… we… we, uh, we dig, uh…
like, a kitchen back… back there.
We blow out this whole wall.
There's a ton of space behind here.
Come on.
There's, like, three floors to look at.
Do you remember the bars
when we were setting up the band?
Mars Bar. It was a port in a storm.
People are still hungry for that, Jake.
It was a million years ago, man.
We were kids.
Okay. Well, restaurants
are the nightclubs of adults.
That's what Black Rabbit would be.
-Black Rabbit?
-Black Rabbit. You like it?
Come here. Look at this. Real fireplace.
-We've got four of 'em.
-Yeah?
Pretty cool. You've got to admit, right?
What do we know
about running a restaurant?
We grew up in a bar.
What are you talking about? Come on.
You know, I have a job.
-We leave this stuff exposed.
-I have a job, Vin.
-Yeah, you carry Wes's luggage.
-Fuck off!
Fuck off. I'm his manager, not his valet.
What's the difference? Tell me.
Jake. Tell you what, you bring him in.
Let him invest.
He's a… he's a huge draw. People love
hangin' out with famous people, not suits.
I'm not a suit.
You're wearing one.
So up here
would be, like…
like, the VIP room.
It'd be one big, open space.
We'd knock out all of these walls.
You know what I mean?
Nice.
DJ booth?
Yeah, DJ. Now you're gettin' it.
Come here. You're gonna love this one.
This is the best part.
Okay. Take a look at this.
Whoa.
It's all ours for the taking.
Hey. Come on.
I'll do it if you say no.
That's your pitch?
We're just talking about us
having something that's our own again.
You know, you've got the grind.
I've got the vision.
We do this right,
we'd have the hottest door in town,
and it would be ours together, you and me.
Tell me you don't miss that.
You know?
You know I do.
"The impossible door
hides what may just be
the finest downtown dining destination
of the past 20 years."
-Whoa!
-Sarah.
One more. Okay.
"The famous clientele
and beautiful waitstaff
assembled by founder Jake Friedken
could compete for one's attention,
but once the food arrives,
the real star enters the constellation."
Okay!
To the chef.
-To three fuckin' stars.
-Stop. Listen to this.
"Stepping inside, you're transported
to a beggar's banquet
that recalls the decadent court
of Mick Jagger and his jesters."
"It's as fresh a design
as I've seen in years."
To the designer.
-Estelle.
-The designer.
Yes!
World's our oyster.
-Partners in crime.
-That was easy.
-Yeah.
-Right?
-Piece of cake. Piece of cake.
So, uh… ready for our second album?
Tomorrow.
I wanna show you something tomorrow.
What about you? You free in the morning?
Which of your assistants do I call?
-Fuck off.
-There's so many.
-You can call me.
-Oh. All right.
'Cause I got somethin'
you're both gonna wanna see.
Heavenly girl, you don't wanna know
The places I've been to
Where you don't wanna go
Everyone says
There's not that many times
You'll save me
Ooh!
People have got to be a little careful
With the rules they make up
I can't, I don't know how to know
How far's too far to go
These rules won't change me
Oh, there I am
My words, mouth wide open
The light in your mind goes
I try to…
No, no, no. I'm… No, I'm just the drummer.
There's the singer.
That's the guy you want.
Oh yes, fuckin' right.
-Get up there, Springsteen.
-Come on, man.
Hey, they want you. Jake!
Yeah, thanks, Jules.
Thank you.
Jake! Jake! Jake! Jake! Jake! Jake!
They want you. Get up there, handsome.
I knew you were a mistake.
Jake! Jake! Jake! Jake!
Jake! Jake! Jake! Jake! Jake!
No fucking way.
Nah!
Boo!
No way.
Oh, you duckin' the spotlight.
You have changed, my brother.
-That's right.
-I kinda wish I knew you guys back then.
It was pretty good.
Uh, what are you drinkin'?
There you go, guys.
What are you drinkin'?
You having some of this?
Mm… I think I'm gonna go home.
I got the crib to myself tonight.
I'm gonna smoke some weed
and read my magazines.
Oh, you outlaw. You be careful.
-Okay. Good night.
-Get home safe.
See you later. You guys need napkins?
-Congrats.
-You too.
Careful, your corks are gonna pop.
-Come on.
-There you go.
-Rox!
-Yeah?
How many glasses?
-Holy shit.
-Yeah.
-This place is a legend.
-Yep.
Damn, Jake. How'd you even get in here?
I knew people who knew people.
Hey, you know… you know who built it?
Yeah. Mies van der Rohe.
-Yeah. Right.
-Yeah.
-Van der Rohe.
-That's right.
There's no way you can afford this.
-I already got the money lined up.
-Huh.
Yeah. Just have to land a few planes.
Did you ask Wes?
I'm gonna tell Wes, but I don't think
there's a part for him in this one.
Oh.
What do you think?
You want me feeding the facelifts?
Yeah.
This is some real rich-people shit, Jake.
How'd you scam your way in?
I told 'em I work with you.
You're a star now.
You deserve the biggest stage.
Better check out the kitchen, then.
Kitchen this way? This way, right?
Yes. Right through there.
Hey, Jake.
What, are you… you gonna steal that thing?
Sh!
-I've never been here before. It's cute.
-Unbelievable.
So what do you need me for?
This place is untouchable. It's a classic.
Classics need reinvention.
And no Wes?
Right?
What?
-Well, it's a big change from the Rabbit.
-Yep.
You know… I'm 50 years old.
I spend another year of my life
closing that bar every night,
and… one morning,
I just maybe won't wake up.
Like my old man.
Are you ready to slow down?
Or grow up.
Wow.
Okay.
You're not really 50, are you?
God.
When did that happen?
I don't know, J.
What? What? Why?
'Cause you got a full plate?
Designing Wes's mother's place…
Which I'm sure is gonna be beautiful,
but come on, this is Yankee Stadium.
You hit a home run here,
and you're New York royalty for life.
Don't you wanna know what you're made of?
You have more talent than I ever did.
I need you.
I needyou.
Sorry, we're actually closed until noon.
Even for, uh… seniors?
Hey, Genny.
What are you doin' here?
Just got back in town.
Okay.
Yeah.
Pretty cool place.
What do you want?
I just…
I wanted to let you know that I was here,
and… and I wanted to see your face.
Here it is.
Is there anything else?
'Cause I have a client coming in.
No, that's it. Um…
You know, I… I don't… I don't expect you
to be happy to see me.
I just wanna let you know I'm here.
Let you know I'm in town,
that I'm thinkin' about
stickin' around, you know?
I'm not sure.
I may, may not.
Your uncle seems to want me to, but…
Uh… So, you know, you wanna talk,
you wanna go see a game,
you wanna drink some coffee,
he knows where to find me, okay?
It'd be great to know how you're doing.
Dad.
Yeah?
Could you please lock the door
on the way out?
Yep.
Thanks.
Nice, Vinnie.
Nice piece of ass you got in there.
-Jesus Christ.
-Little young for you, though, isn't she?
What, you guys miss me?
I thought we said five.
Yeah, well, since you don't got a watch…
We wanna check on our investment.
You don't have the best record.
Well, I'm going to get it right now.
Why don't you guys go get a snack?
-You know what they say about me, Vinnie?
-What's that?
Fool me once, you know…
Just don't fuckin' do that!
-Goddamn it.
-Careful, Vinnie. This shit gets messy.
She don't want you all messed up, Vinnie.
-Fuckin'…
-Five o'clock tonight.
-…dicks.
-Don't be late.
Hunter snaps his iPad shut real quick,
shoves it under his pillow.
He was jerking it, huh?
Well, I go back,
I check his search history.
The last thing he typed was,
"Fluffy Vietnamese chicks."
-Very nice. So he's a freak, huh?
-Well, that's what I thought.
Val… Two weeks later,
Val gets a box in the mail.
A mini incubator
full of eggs from Vietnam.
-What?
-Baby chickens.
-So he's a super freak, huh?
-No, he's my sweet boy.
He's just nothing like you. Or me.
Well, nothing like me
means you're doin' somethin' wrong.
We're late. Like, where are these guys?
-Um, is he good otherwise?
-Yeah, he's good.
Got really into dance.
-Dance?
-He's talented too.
I can't tell if he's got any taste though.
-Jesus, the music.
-Sounds like he needs an older brother.
-What are you doing? You cleaning it now?
-I stepped in a puddle.
Yeah, You know
Wes says these are worth 2,000 bucks?
Oh.
-You look ridiculous.
-No, I don't.
These are pretty sweet,
and I'll look real smart once I sell 'em.
I asked him for a pair for you. He says
they just don't make 'em super small.
Fuck you.
I can buy my own shoes.
Um… Hey, listen.
Uh…
Remember you asked me
to think about stickin' around?
Uh… I'm thinkin' about it.
-For real?
-Yeah, I went, and I saw Gen.
Good.
Yeah, yeah, she's…
she seems great, and…
Maybe I make a fresh start. I don't know.
-I've said it before.
-It's never too late, man.
I'm thinking.
-Especially now you got the shoes.
-Yeah.
-That your guy?
-We're all standing here waiting.
-Where are you?
-Where are the others?
-You're kidding. What?
-That's the attorney, huh?
Isaac.
Don't. He's legitimate.
Really?
Did you get a deal on this guy?
-What?
-They're not coming.
They can't get a C of O.
The inspector found electrical issues.
-What's a C of O?
-Certificate of Occupancy.
The report says the wiring'sverkackt.
The place is a tinderbox.
They wanna lower the offer.
-Fuck that.
-To what?
Six twenty-five.
That… No. We don't make a penny.
That's break even.
There were contingencies in the contract.
-They have an out, and they want it.
-How did that happen?
You had one offer in six months.
They had leverage.
You signed the contract.
Hey. Um, when you said, uh… break even,
what does that mean?
That's… Is that no cash for us?
You could fix it,
put it back on the market--
No, I can't wait for that.
I got no time for that.
-Do we get any cash out of that?
-We say…
we say yes to this shit, when do we…
when do we… when do we close?
Eesh… It'll be a few weeks at least.
-I gotta re-paper it and…
-Yeah, you gonna pay for that?
I'm sorry.
-Not good enough.
-It's a… it's adarachfall.
-Is that good?
-Eh!
You think about it. You call me.
I thought about it. I think you suck.
Fuck.
What are you pissed about?
You're loaded. I'm fuckin' dead.
You're not the only one
with problems, Vin.
For fuck's sake.
The money was supposed to be
in my account 15 minutes ago.
Wait, you're dead?
-What do you mean you're dead?
-Don't worry about it.
-Still in the shit?
-Drive the car.
You fucking idiot.
Are you still in the shit? Fucking moron.
Hey, hey. Who the fuck
do you think you're talking to?
What?
Call me that one more fuckin' time!
That's what I thought.
Better watch your fucking mouth, Jake.
-Save it for someone who'll take it.
-Can I have my keys?
For fuck's sake.
Hey, you better be at the Rabbit later!
-Jake.
-Hey.
My God.
-What's up, man?
-Hey.
Just stopped by to take a look
at the finances.
-I wanna introduce you to my accountant.
-Oh, did we say today?
-Yeah, is that a problem?
-No, man. No, no.
You just caught me, uh…
you just caught me, uh… in top gear.
-Jake. Nice to meet you.
-Pleasure. Sheri.
You know what?
Actually, in truth, I hate to do this. Uh…
Things have gotten crazy since the review.
My phone's ringin' off the fuckin' hook.
-That's fuckin' amazing.
-Give me a couple of days?
-Just a couple of days.
-Of course. Yeah, man.
This is what it looks like
when your life's at the top, all right?
You're about to pah-pop.
It gets bigger, you get busier.
That's what I'm learning. Like our coffee?
-It's pretty good coffee.
-Pretty good?
Get out of here. Just go.
More of that when we sit down,
couple of days.
-Okay.
-We gotta get a jump on that spot.
-That's right. I'm on it, no doubt.
-Okay.
Anna, it's Jake.
What the fuck?
I'm… That is some childish shit.
My son follows you, so thanks for that.
Call me back.
But I mean, how does it feel? Three stars
is unheard of for a place like this.
Are you handling the spotlight?
We're good on the pictures.
-Let's finish the rest out front.
-Okay.
How does it feel?
Well, this morning
I updated the laundry order,
reviewed time cards,
I scrubbed the grout behind the fryer.
Glamorous.
This job doesn't allow
a lot of time for reflection,
but I'm really proud of my team
and everything we achieved
here in this meat dungeon.
Nah, Meat Dungeon is in Chelsea.
I passed out there once.
-Rox.
-Yeah?
Great. You got a minute?
I… I… I… I got a question for you.
Uh, yeah, sure, but do you know Lisa
fromNew York Magazine?
She's, uh… doing a profile on me.
About time. Lisa Klein, right?
-Yes.
-Jake.
-Hi.
I was just hearing how you keep
your star chef locked in this dungeon?
Oh, please.
Well, yeah. No, I mean, come on.
She… she knew what she was
getting herself into.
-That true?
-Yeah.
Dying to hear how you two met,
but I'll let you do what you need to.
No, no, this can wait. Sit down.
Uh… what do you want? Water? Soda?
-Yeah, water. Thank you.
-Scotch?
-Hey.
-You're home early.
What kind of cash you got on hand?
Cheap bastards.
Don't appreciate talent.
No, this is not a joke, okay? I am…
I am fucked.
Really fucked.
-Mancuso?
-Yeah. Yeah.
-Can Jake help?
-Mm? Mm-mm.
Jake's not an option.
Do you know anyone running a game?
Uh… what's today? Wednesday.
Yeah. Maybe Sigman.
I'll check. He's got his thing
set up downtown right now.
-Downtown? He's not in Queens anymore?
-No, he moved up.
COVID shit. You'll see.
-But you have to wear a tie.
-Mm.
You sure you don't have any cash
in a safe or something?
Safe? No.
Uh… sorry. I'm…
I'm all tapped out.
-Best I can offer is a pick-me-up.
-No. No, no. No thank you.
Just text me that address
when you get it, okay?
I think that's it.
Thanks again for your time.
Um… I'd love to talk to some staff
to follow up, get some backstory--
You have my number.
Anyone you wanna talk to, just call me.
-Okay, that'd be great.
-Thank you.
Um… thanks again. Enjoy your well-wishes.
-You're welcome. Thanks.
-Thanks.
-Bye now.
-Bye.
I think I'm gonna need
some media training.
You seen this post Anna made?
What the fuck is this?
-"Beware"?
-She won't answer my calls.
Will you talk to her?
She won't fuckin' talk to me.
What is she doing?
Well, I'm guessing she's pissed
'cause I fired her, but I…
What was I supposed to do?
She bagged two shifts.
You know, Tony said
she was wasted that night.
I don't think this is venting.
So call her.
This could spook the Pool Room investors.
You know, we have to have
our shit dialed in.
They can't say no.
Hmm? People are watching, you know?
Call her?
Yeah.
-Yeah, I'm on it.
-Thanks.
Guess who's home?
Hey.
Look at that face.
Get over here, you stunner.
I didn't think
you were coming back till tomorrow.
Them Hollywood chuckleheads trying
to burn it down every night, whereas I
am just trying to get back
to you.
What you doing?
Are you busy? Am I interrupting?
-Yeah, I'm doing a bit of work.
-Work? What are you working on?
Um… well, just Jake, uh… wants
to take over The Pool Room.
Uptown?
-A'ight. Hustling?
-Yeah, he's asked me to design it.
Boo. No, thank you. You're far too busy.
Well, I'm kinda interested.
I mean, the place is a landmark, so…
So why does he need you?
I mean, don't get me wrong.
I'm sure you would class that joint out,
but you don't have to.
Just because Jake gave you
your break or whatever.
Besides, you've got,
like, four projects on already,
and we need to finish the Hamptons house.
And, baby girl, this team?
They are on smoke.
They wanna use my voice in a Pixar movie.
I might go home
and play Glastonbury next year,
and Gucci are interested in collaborating.
Like, it's all poppin' off,
and I need my girl on my arm
making me look handsome and shit.
Plus…
I want us to get started
havin' this little family of ours.
'Cause I cannot be
40 years old
changing diapers.
You're not changing diapers
no matter how old you are.
Straight facts.
But I'm trying to get into yours.
-You're disgusting.
-I love you.
Mr. Williams?
There's a Mr. Friedken here to see you.
Let him in.
Maybe he's here to beg.
Fuck.
Oh,thatMr. Friedken. This'll be fun.
Hey.
Hi, Estelle, um…
It's cool if just Wes and I…
-This is a little embarrassing.
-Yeah, sure. I'll make some tea.
Thanks.
-What's up, big bro? You okay?
-Yeah.
Need another pair of kicks?
Uh… Um…
I hate to do this, but, um…
I gotta borrow some cash.
Lose another bet on the tables?
-No.
-Roof?
No.
You're lucky I love you, man,
and you caught me in a good mood.
Let me see what I've got for you.
I'm holding, like, 2,500. That cover you?
Uh… y…
This is great, uh, but…
Uh…
I'm in a… I'm in a pretty big hole. Um…
I gotta borrow, like, 30 grand.
It's just a loan.
V, you got me fucked up.
Do I look like a Wells Fargo?
No. No, no. I don't mean any disrespect.
-How long have we known each other?
-A long time.
I don't run that kinda operation.
I'm a businessman.
I design clothes. I make music.
I'm not on street corners makin' handouts.
What the fuck have you got yourself into?
Wes.
Forget that I asked. I'm sorry.
This is great. I'll pay you back.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
-Wait.
-Yep.
-Look, do I need to talk to Jake?
-Uh, no, no.
No. No. Please don't.
But…
…do you have a tie I can borrow?
Do you have a tie in this bag?
-He's not comin'.
-Should we go tell him?
We got a problem.
Who?
Vince. Friedken.
I know you said that he's…
But…
How much?
Tell him.
One-forty.
Look, he had stacks. Okay? I don't know.
He was paying.
He was a good mark.
I fucking told you he's out,
and now he owes us 140 grand?
Okay…
What did you want me to do?
I'm trying to be independent.
You know?
Build my own book
and expand the business.
Well, if this is your business,
then why are you coming to me?
'Cause now he's back in town,
acting like the rules don't apply, and…
You're supposed to keep a leash
on this kid.
Dad, I know you have ties with Vince, but
I need you tell me it's okay
if I gotta turn up the heat.
You understand? Like…
What are people gonna think?
We let him walk with that debt?
-What'd he say there at the end?
-He said find him.
Take the gloves off.
Anybody seen Vince?
Anybody?
Mel, did you call him?
I don't have his number.
You told me never to call him.
Yeah. Fuck.
Okay. Tell Joe
he's gotta cover upstairs in the bar
till I get back from this school thing.
You're a great dad.
It runs in my family.
If you see Vince,
tell him I'm gonna kill him.
Can I help you with something?
Yeah. It's Vince. Matt's friend.
Hello.
You're not alive
Until you start kickin'
When the room is spinnin'
And the words aren't stickin'
And the radio
Is all about a runaway model
With a face like sin
And a heart like a James Joyce novel
Saying "Sister, sister
How I missed ya, missed ya"
"Let's go wrist to wrist
And take the skin off of the blister"
-Knock 'em dead, pal.
-If you're a rock star
Pornstar, superstar
Doesn't matter what you are
Get yourself a good car
-Get outta here
-No more bets.
Well
But the boys in the better land
You're always talkin'
'Bout the boys in the better land…
-Six, black.
-The boys in the better land
But the boys in the better land
You're always talkin'
'Bout the boys in the better la--
Hunter.
-Oh, hey, Dad.
-Hey, what'd I miss? Hi. Hey, how are ya?
Oh, great. Sorry, stuck at work.
-Did you make that?
-Kind of.
-Well, I wanna show you robotics.
-Sure.
-Okay.
-Come on.
You lead. Sorry. Vince is back.
-I know. Hunter said.
-Yeah.
How's he doing?
Oh, fine, you know.
-Sorry.
-Great. Settling right back in.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-Vince?
Hey. Something really exciting's happened.
-Okay.
-Big opportunity for me.
Wanted to share it with you.
This is, uh… you know,
for your ears only, okay?
I got an in on The Pool Room.
You know? The restaurant Four Seasons.
Yeah, yeah. No, I know.
So you wanna open up another spot?
Yeah, but this is bigger than that.
Now, I need a float
to tie up some loose ends.
Listen, if you're in some kind of trouble…
-No.
-…or you need a loan--
This is an investment for you.
You know? One hundred and we're all set.
-Thousand?
-You're the first one in.
It's a sure thing, Val.
I could double my income overnight.
Imagine that. That would be good
for all of us, right?
If you're overextended,
just don't pay the tuition.
-No, no, no.
-My parents have offered to.
It's totally separate. Totally separate.
He's my son.
That's Hunter. This is… this is business.
Then why are you asking me
and not your investors?
Because it's fluid.
'Cause calendars are off.
You know, there's a gap
between what they need and what I have.
-Timing. It's optics.
-What are you talking about?
The restaurant business
is very messy, Val.
-Oh, is it?
-Val. Yeah. It's not black and white.
This is a real shot for me.
You know, I get this, I don't need to be
the last guy standing
at the party every night.
I get to slow down.
And it would be mine.
Not Wes's. Not Vince's. It would be mine.
-Guys, come here. I need to show you this!
-Yeah, coming.
I know you want this.
It's you.
Always reaching
for the next rung on the ladder.
Easy for you to say, right?
Born on the top floor.
I hope you get what you want.
But I can't invest in you
anymore, you know?
Come on now. Here we come.
Lucky seven now.
Wanna free my mind…
It's unbelievable.
This fucking guy can't lose.
Damn right, I can't lose.
No one's losing tonight.
Leave your money up there, all right?
Here, I need you to blow on these.
Blow on those. Come on.
No, hot air. Warm 'em up. Warm 'em up.
There it is. Perfect. Watch this.
Tell me if I win.
Wanna free my mind…
Sounds like a win. Sounds pretty good.
Unbelievable.
I mean, it's fantastic, right?
Who doesn't love craps? Here we go!
No bets. There we go.
Come on!
Oh yeah.
Thank you.
Hey, guys. Uh, what's the name?
Uh… nah. Um… I'm friends with Vince.
Is he here or…
I don't know.
-Let me check.
-Yeah, you go check. We'll be right here.
Can you get two more bottles, please?
And one, two, three, four, five…
Where's Amir? Six. Six burgers.
Anyone want anything else?
Don't wave your hand at me
when I know you're hungry.
Bring the caviar just in case.
Nothing happening
Nothing at all, thanking…
Hey, I need two more bottles
of the Barolo.
Is that for Wes?
And the burgers and the caviar.
It's been like this all night.
Did he put down a card?
You mean tonight or this month?
Uh, I need three espresso martinis.
…on your Cartier
Holding hands and
Waiting for the rare changes
Take us out of the loop
So romantic…
-Hey.
-Hey, do you want a glass?
-You should grab a seat.
-I'm working.
Meet Amir and dem man from "Nyke".
"Nike-ee." I get it.
They wanna do another collaboration.
-Can we talk?
-Yeah.
Okay. Just give me a second.
One minute, guys. Oh, I'm comin'.
Bro, Where is Vin?
I want them to see him in my kicks.
He's taken the night off.
I don't know. Hey, look.
Can you put down a card?
You're running a pretty heavy bill.
-Are you serious right now?
-Come on.
None of this is free, right?
The Barolo? Four hundred a bottle.
Yeah. You think Steinbrenner
pays for hot dogs at the Yankees?
What the fuck, man? I own this place.
Weown it.
Right? We own it.
Steinbrenner's dead.
-Hmm.
-I'm trying to turn a profit.
Is everything okay?
-Mm?
-You and Vin got something going on?
'Cause I'm getting
the full freakin' experience today.
What? What does that mean?
Well, earlier on, big bro
tried to shake me down for 30 stacks.
Okay. I don't know anything about that.
Do you know anything about The Pool Room?
You trying to steal my girl?
-I was… I was gonna tell you.
-It's okay. She's busy, but it's okay.
There's enough apple pie
to go around for everyone.
-Hmm.
-Come, sit, have a drink.
You can put it on my tab.
Fuck.
Seriously, calm down.
Sweaty's not a good look on you.
Cheers!
You're Mancuso's boy, right?
And you're, uh, Fuckhead's brother. Right?
Vince isn't here,
so can I help you with somethin'?
-When's he coming in?
-I don't know. Not tonight.
I can't have you standing there.
People don't stand here?
If they're coming in,
but you're leaving, so…
Not even a drink?
What if I'm thirsty? What if I'm… snacky?
Nah, you know what? Fuck this place.
All right? And fuck you too.
We'll find him.
Not a problem.
-It's a nice place.
-Thanks.
Check it out. He's on a run at Sigman's.
Mm-hmm. Oh, how nice.
Three tens. Perfect.
-Eighteen. Blackjack.
-Ooh!
-Look at that!
-Twenty.
This lucky son of a bitch
is up, like, 75 grand.
-Nineteen.
-Oh boy.
Well, we got it two thirds right
at this table.
Congratulations, and to me too.
Let's see. Oh boy.
Just stacks of orange everywhere, huh?
Who doesn't love orange?
Place your bets.
Let's go big or go home.
All right.
All right, let's do this. Here we go.
Good start.
Seventeen.
Fifteen.
You're not gonna hit that, are you?
Seventeen against a seven…
Come on.
That's a great decision.
Good decision.
You're doubling on a fucking 15
with 75 grand?
-Yeah, sure am.
-Are you crazy?
No, I'm not, Chatty.
I'm fuckin' blessed. Here we go.
-Twenty.
-Look at that!
Holy shit! A hundred and fifty grand.
Hang on, hang on. You're not gonna
take his bust card, right?
Leave it.
That's a 17 against a seven just like her.
What'd she do?
-Table's hot, man. Let's go. Double down.
-Are you kidding me?
-Bust.
-Motherfuck…
Come on, it's time to go.
-Good night.
-Hang on.
Where are you goin'? Sit tight.
You're gonna watch the rest of this.
Fourteen.
-Fifteen.
-You still got this. Let's go.
-Twenty-one.
-Un-fucking-real.
Un-fucking-real.
What's that? Is that a fuckin' grin?
Was that a fucking grin?
Is that all you got?
You don't have my $150,000?
You stupid motherfucker!
Whoa! Hey, hey, hey.
-Night.
-Good night.
Keep an eye on him.
It's a lot of success
for a young man to deal with.
Oh yeah?
What would you know about that?
I'm kidding. You created the monster.
You signed him.
Yeah, I wish
I still had 5% of the monster.
Yeah, I bet you do.
So, listen, I'm sorry I blew up your spot
about the restaurant.
-What did he say?
-That you weren't gonna do it.
-Oh, he did?
-Yeah.
Well, you know,
he doesn't think it's a good time.
I didn't ask what he wants. I asked you.
And what do you want?
'Cause I really wanted
to do this with you.
-I did.
-I wanna do it.
I am doin' it.
So…
Yeah?
Yeah, let's do it.
We were rootin' for you, Vince.
Hey.
Don't make a scene, okay?
Just get the fuck up.
Let's go. I'm not askin'.
-Oh fuck! Fucking shit.
-Motherfucker!
Fuck.
-Fuck!
-Fuck.
-Go!
Shit!
Fuck.
Yo! Fuck! Jesus. God, you're killing me.
Run! Go! Fuck off of me!
-Fuck!
-Fuck you! Go!
Yo!
Shit.
Yeah, where you gonna go, bitch?
Fuck this shit!
Go!
Will you fucking help me?
Fuck!
Fuck.
Come on, come on.
Come on, motherfucker!
Oh yes!
What are you doing, man?
You piece of shit!
Goddamn it!
I don't have it!
Yeah, no shit! Got him.
-Yeah, no shit!
-Get the fuck off me.
You got me all gross and sweaty,
you dumb fuck!
You broke your promise, Vince.
-We're gonna keep ours.
-No, you're not.
-You're not a fuckin' butcher.
-Give it to me.
-Get the fuck off me.
-Give me that fuckin' pinky.
Take a fuckin' breath!
-Give me the fuckin' pinky!
-What's that? Mom's home!
-Go.
-What now, you stupid ass?
End of the round, huh? Get off me, dick.
Take the next one.
Let's fire up that mop.
I'll see you on one, my friend.
-Let's go.
-Who the fuck is this guy?
-Come on, Junior. Come on. Please!
-Get his fucking hand out!
Please leave it! Give me two more days!
-Sit still or it's all of 'em coming off.
-Leave it!
Damn it!
-You're hittin' fuckin' bone!
-I know what I'm fuckin' hitting!
Well, fucking lean on it!
I am fucking putting it…
Jesus! Fuck!
Gah!
I know that shit hurt,
but you need to listen to me, Vince.
Because if you don't get us
our fuckin' money,
the next person we hurt
is not you.
You understand?
Yeah.
Hello?
Yeah, Jake? We gotta talk.
Yeah, come up.
I should've fuckin' told you.
I know.
You said to my face you'd squared it.
Yeah.
What did you do with that loan
you took on Mom's house way back?
Huh?
Doubled down.
I thought I could pay these guys back.
Had a sure thing.
Julius fuckin' Randle, Jake.
You bet Mom's money on the Knicks?
A lot of people bet the Knicks, Jake.
They're a professional basketball team.
And the money you got from the restaurant?
-The one you and Naveen kicked me out of?
-Bailed you out. Bailed you out.
Saved your fuckin' ass.
You gambled that too, right?
Then you go down to Junior,
take a loan on the house,
you bet it again, and lost it all.
And then you skip town.
Sound right?
Sounds like the least favorable way
you could possibly phrase it,
but yeah, you're all caught up.
And… I gotta ask
'cause the suspense is fucking killing me,
what happened to your shoes, Vince?
I got a sweet number on the bus.
Yeah.
-You sold your fuckin' shoes?
-Yeah.
I took 500 bucks,
and I'm fucking chipping away at it.
-I'm doing my fuckin' part, Giggles.
-Yeah.
Okay? I did it on my way home
from getting my fuckin' finger chopped off
by those goddamn fuckin' zeros
who say Gen is next.
You're helping me.
They said that?
They said Gen is next?
-That's exactly what they said.
-How much do you owe 'em, Vince?
One-forty.
Big number.
140 grand?
-It's a big number. There was juice.
-Fuck me.
Fuck me. Jesus.
Ain't such a big number
for you, Big Deals.
Look at this spot. Pretty sweet.
-It's a rental.
-So?
It's a rental, and I'm four months behind.
-Yeah.
-What's that mean? Pay your bills.
-Fuckin' sell that sweet whip.
-Do not give me financial advice.
What sweet whip?
The Jag? It's falling apart.
The electrics are shot.
Rear windows don't work.
I'd get what? Four grand, five grand.
Okay. Jake's broke? Come on.
You fuckin' broke?
I… I… I have child support.
Right? Tuition, fucking bills.
Hunter needed braces.
And Gen had a tight couple of months,
right? It's okay. I took care of her.
It's okay. I'm… I'm holding on
by the skin of my teeth.
I didn't budget for you.
Why did I let you back in?
Well, don't do it for me, okay?
Why don't you do it for Gen? My daughter.
Your niece.
-Come on.
-Fuck.
Your fuckin' niece.
Come on.
Come on. Let's fuckin' think about it.
We gotta do somethin', Uncle Jake.
You know?
Oh Christ.
Or I fuckin' eat a gun, you know?
And I just end it.
For both of us.
Cheap.
Shut up. Who cleans up that mess?
-Hey.
-I didn't think you were coming.
-Yeah, I'm not staying.
I gotta, um,
get these to…
You here 'cause Jake sent you,
or you were worried
I'm gonna ruin the book deal or…
I… What?
If you're here about the fuckin' post,
I took it down.
No, I'm fuckin'…
I'm here as your friend.
What the fuck is goin' on?
Great friend.
Yeah.
I know. I… It got busy.
-I should've reached out when you left.
-I got fired, actually.
Jake said you missed two shifts.
It was the biggest night of our life.
Did I do something?
'Cause that post was pretty harsh.
Do you wanna tell me what's goin' on?
Anna.
What happened?
Honestly, I don't even know.
Uh…
So the last night I was there, right,
it was late, and, um,
there was, like, a few of us
still at the bar. We were having drinks.
Jules had been up there all night.
Wouldn't shut the fuck up, you know?
-You know what he's like.
-Yeah.
And he kept trying
to get me to join him, and I…
Like, I put him off, and I put him off,
and then I finally fucking, like…
Like, I just… I had a drink with him.
It was just…
I've been a bartender
for fuckin' 15 years.
You know I can hang.
I do not, like, black out. That's not…
The next thing I remember,
I'm, like, waking up on the bathroom floor
and my clothes are, like,
in a ball in the corner,
and I don't remember what happened and…
but I just know it wasn't good.
I'm sorry.
I take it you didn't tell Jake.
No. I was confused.
Do you wanna tell him now?
Why?
Tanya told him
Jules put his fuckin' hand up her skirt,
and Jake didn't do anything, so…
Roxie.
You know what goes on up there. You…
You see how they treat us.
Do you ever do anything?
Jesus. What can I do?
You wanna fuckin' press charges?
No. I just want it to go away.
-Are you sure?
-Yeah.
'Cause, listen, if you wanna go after him,
I'm fuckin' with you all the way.
I got your back.
It's too fuckin' late.
Fuck.
Yo! Can I help you with somethin'?
Can't have you standing there.
This way.
Come on. He's waitin'.
He… he says you look
even more like your mom now.
Want a drink?
Sure.
Lou, get us a couple of coffees.
So the word on the street
is the restaurant business
is going well, huh?
-Yeah.
-Mm?
He said your pops would be proud.
-You followed in his footsteps.
-Hmm.
I hope I get a few more than he did.
He said good thing
you, uh, take after your mom.
Yeah.
Your brother, Vince,
on the other hand, you know…
He told me not to give Vince
a line of credit, but, you know…
You understand what this all means, right?
-Yeah.
-This… this meeting?
Yeah, I know.
It means… it means it's… it's on me.
It's mine. The situation is mine.
Yeah.
So what's the plan?
-What's the plan?
-Yeah.
What's the plan?
The plan… the plan is
your loser deadbeat brother owes us 140.
-Yeah.
-Right?
And now you owe us, wait for it, 140.
Did you follow that?
It's due immediately.
Like, now. It's simple.
With respect…
with respect, it's a lot of money,
and I need… I need a little bit of time.
He needs more time.
He's two fucking years late.
Just a little bit of time.
-All right. Time's up. This is bullshit.
-Come on.
Come on.
He's asking what can you do?
Yeah, so I have 20.
-Twenty.
-Easy.
-And I can give you that every week.
-A fuckin' payment plan?
-Until we're whole.
-No, you fuckin' prick.
-Every week until we're whole.
-No, no.
What does he say?
He says he knows you,
and he trusts you because you're smart.
Thank you.
So fuck it, we'll… we'll do it.
-Twenty grand a week until we're square.
-Yeah.
But if you're late one single day,
if you come to us and you say,
"Oh, hey, Joe, I'm so sorry,"
I mean, that's it.
There's no… no conversation.
-Yeah.
-All right?
-The restaurant, it's… it's ours.
The restaurant?
That's… No.
It's not. No shot. It's not on the table.
Fuck! Ah!
Ow! Shit! Shit!
Oh Christ!
He's calling the shots now, you see,
so he'll decide
what's on the fuckin' table.
And he's only doing this favor
'cause of your mom,
but if you Friedken brothers
fuck us again,
he's not holding me back anymore. Huh?
First payment's due Monday.
Four days? That's not a week.
"Four days? That's not a week."
What? It's not a week.
He said, "See? I told him you were smart."
Yeah, right.
Thank you.
He's sorry that it's come to this,
but, you know,
your brother has a real problem,
and he says I don't listen.
And unfortunately for us,
we don't choose our own families.
-So? What did he say?
-We're fucked.